http://www.guitarstop.com/privacy-policy

Private Music Lessons: Guitar, Bass, Banjo, Mandolin, Piano, Ukulele, & Voice HomeShopShopping GuideRepairsLessonsRecitalsShippingReturn PolicyAbout UsContactMoreHomeShopShopping GuideRepairsLessonsRecitalsShippingReturn PolicyAbout UsContactHomeShopShopping GuideRepairsLessonsRecitalsShippingReturn PolicyAbout UsContactFamily Musical Instrument Guitar Store & Lessons
Cambridge MA - Since 1962Family Musical Instrument Guitar Store & Lessons
Cambridge MA - Since 1962Family Musical Instrument Guitar Store & Lessons
Cambridge MA - Since 1962
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an  order,  or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address,  mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information? We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products,  surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To   personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of  content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To  quickly process your transactions.
How do we protect visitor information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"? Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service. Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include  Guitar Stop. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us? To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Changes to our policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. Questions and feedback We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. Online Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. Your consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Privacy PolicyTermsGuitar Stop®1760 Massachusetts Ave,
Cambridge, Massachusetts 02140, United States(617) 876-0687
-
info@guitarstop.comCopyright © 2020 Guitar Stop - All Rights Reserved.Monday- Saturday 10:00 am - 6:00 pm
